Today, we
saw a significant negative momentum in ICICI Lombard. However, if
we consider its delivery report
and
look at it, we may see positive
movement. So,
before we proceed with the delivery report, let me tell you that
I have selected some levels in the will.
These levels appear to be breaking out, so
we may see a slightly faster movement on the positive or negative side.
Friends, this is your
first visit to this YouTube channel,
so I request you with folded hands to
like the video, subscribe to the channel, and
click the notification bell
so that
you continue to receive such market-related videos.
Friends, you all know that
all income generated from this YouTube channel will be donated to cow welfare.
Therefore, please give this YouTube channel your love and
support. So, friends, first of all, let's
talk about the delivery
report. You can see it here.
Friends, here you have the data for August 6th. Along with this, the
stocks that trended here throughout the day.  The shares that have been delivered are
around 18 lakh 52 thousand
358 and along with this
friends, if you look at the delivery quantity here,
you can see that
around 11011 lakh 10 thousand 690
shares have been delivered here, whose percentage is around
seven percent or so, which is
much higher than its previous trading session, so
friends, there can be a possibility here
that now around the level or mid which it is getting
or around the level where it has
taken its closing today, then from here
we can again see a movement on the positive side
and by the way,
friends, talk about its signal here, then the
level around which it has given its closing,
you can see that your
negative movement is of Rs 1214 friends
and the closing given in it is of 1218
paise in the Panchayat, so if
I talk about the signal as per my understanding, then
we can still see a negative movement here, according to which
we have
seen its closing, so
friends, let's talk about some new
Before talking about the labels, let me tell you that the
video is for educational purposes only. You
must take advice from your advisor before buying or selling. Along with this, if
you have not yet liked this video
or subscribed to the channel,
then I request you with folded hands to
like the video, subscribe to the channel and
definitely turn on the notification bell so that
you will keep getting such videos related to the market. So
friends, first of all I will talk about the
resistance area here,
so you can see here that the first
resistance area
is around Rs. 1235 after applying 1229, which you
can see here, so friends, here
we get to see the opening of the negative side from 1222,
so the first negative movement can happen
here around Rs. 1213 and
along with this the level gives a breakout of 1210,
so after that we can see the
possibility of negative moment around Rs. 1200 here.
Along with this, friends, from this level
we can see the closing of the down side.  If we see this, then the
support level that is left with us is
around Rs.1100
and from this level the dance and comment shows us, then
after that we can see the negative moment
quite fast here,
whose area can be
around Rs.1100 to Rs.1165 and
we can see this moment quite fast,
while talking about the movement of its positive
side,
if the level here gives respect, which has its
negative side works, if we
create it in it, friends, then the
area around 1222 to 1214,
if this video is used as a support level,
and the most
important thing friends, if you give opening of your side from 1225, then it can be a
positive
signal for us for some morning channels,
so friends, here the first level
gives breakout, after giving opening of Rs.1222, the
level of 1226 gives breakout,
so the first positive moment is from Rs.1229 to
This level may be around 1235, if it is successful in using it as a support level, then the possibility
of positive moment after that, the
first possibility can be around Rs. 1238 to Rs. 1243 and the
second possibility is that after both these levels are
pregnant, it can be around Rs. 1250 and
along with this
friends, till we do
not see a closing of Rs. 1253, this
area around Rs. 1250
is a resistance level
friends and from here we can get to
see moments of the negative side at any time, which can be
quite fast, so friends, if
you liked the video, then please like this video,
subscribe to the channel and
definitely send the notification so that
you keep getting such videos related to the market and
along with this, friends, thank you very much for
giving your valuable time for this video,
friends, see you in the next video, Jai
Hind